lcwu.edu.pk 2011-10-07

# Privacy Policy - LCWU

**Privacy Policy**

LCWU is fully committed to providing an informative, useful website for its visitors. The university enjoys interacting with its audience and helping to provide it with pertinent information. Visitors to any webpage have an opportunity to contact us via E-mail. 

The policy of LCWU’s officially controlled and operated WWW sites is to respect and protect the privacy of its students, faculty, staff, and all other users. LCWU does not sell or distribute any information obtained from our visitors to a third party, under any circumstance. 

This policy defines how LCWU collects information from you and how it is used. For each visitor to LCWU's website, the following information is collected:   

  * Internet addressing information of visitors to our Web pages (IP Addresses) 
  * The e-mail addresses of those who communicate with us via e-mail 
  * The aggregate information on what pages visitors access or visit 
  * Information volunteered by the visitor, such as survey information 
  * Personal information we request for information inquiries/requests, etc. 

The collected information is used for internal University purposes and may be used to improve the content of LCWU's overall website. It will not be shared with other organizations to help them contact visitors. However, LCWU reserves the right to use the information to contact visitors for marketing purposes. 

A small number of LCWU pages contain links which may take you outside of our website. Users should be aware that when you are on LCWU website, and you "click" on a banner advertisement, you will be directed to another website which is beyond LCWU's control. These other sites may send and receive cookies, collect data, or solicit personal information and may use this information in ways LCWU does not in accordance with its privacy policy statement. Always be aware of whose site you are visiting. 

While LCWU strives to protect its users' personal information and privacy, it cannot guarantee the security of any information you disclose online and you do so at your own risk. LCWU's policy does not extend to anything that is inherent in the operation of the Internet, and therefore beyond our control, and is not to be applied in any manner contrary to applicable law or governmental regulation. 

LCWU reserves the right at its discretion to make changes to this policy at any time. Feel free to check this page periodically for amendments/updates
